mixstep.co 2017-06-27

# Mixstep - Free Audio Hosting Service

This Mixstep Privacy Policy, in conjunction with the AUP, Terms of Service and other terms and conditions of use which are incorporated herein by reference and may be posted and applicable to specific services, governs your use of the Mixstep website and are collectively referred to as the "Agreement".

Mixstep may modify the Agreement which will become effective immediately upon posting on the website. Your continued use of the website and any associated services, the "Services", indicates your acceptance of the Agreement.

Any Content uploaded by you to Mixstep becomes published Content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy.

Mixstep uses IP addresses to measure usage and analyze trends, administer the website and collect information for its databases.

We will not rent, sell or share your information with third parties. However, we may disclose your personal information or any of its log file information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such actions are necessary to: conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on us; protect and defend the rights or property of Mixstep, or visitors of Mixstep; identify persons who may be violating the law, the legal notice, or the rights of third parties; co-operate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities.

Third-party websites linked to Mixstep are not covered by this Privacy Policy. These websites may collect personally identifiable information about you and place a cookie on your browser. Mixstep is not responsible for the privacy practices of the third-party websites and companies.

Mixstep is not responsible if you volunteer personal information online that is accessible to the public. You may receive unsolicited messages from other parties or it may be used in a manner that violates the law, your personal privacy or your safety. By submitting such information, you assume the risks and sole liability arising as a result of such information being displayed.

If you are not a resident of the Germany, you understand and agree that Mixstep stores and processes your information on computers located in the Germany, any by providing any data to Mixstep, you consent to the transfer of such information to Germany.

In the event that Mixstep is acquired or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right to transfer or assign the information we have collected from you as part of any change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, Mixstep may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred or used.

Although we strive to protect your personal information, Mixstep cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.
